Friendship is the ultimate upgrade
Next Gen is a animation, action, adventure film directed by Kevin R. Adams.
A friendship with a top-secret robot turns a lonely girl's life into a thrilling
adventure as they take on bullies, evil bots and a scheming madman.
Project 77 (voice), played by John Krasinski.
Mai (voice), played by Lo Mutuc.
Justin Pin / Ares (voice), played by Jason Sudeikis.
Momo (voice), played by Michael Peña.
Dr. Tanner Rice / Q-Bots (voice), played by David Cross.
Molly (voice), played by Constance Wu.
Next Gen is a 2018 animated science fiction action film based on the online manhua 7723 by Wang Nima (which was
originally published in Baozou Manhua, which Wang founded and led), and directed by Kevin R.
Adams and Joe Ksander.
Starring the voices of Charlyne Yi, John Krasinski, Jason Sudeikis, Michael Peña, David Cross and Constance Wu, the film tells the story of a lonely rebellious teenage girl living in a world where sentient
robot technology is commonplace, and a top-secret weaponized robot, who, through a chance encounter, meet each other and form an unlikely bond that they must use to stop a vicious threat.
It was released on Netflix on September 7, 2018, and was
produced almost exclusively using Blender.
The film explores themes of friendship, protection,
bully, memory, female protagonist.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking and intense.